Guide to the Division of Student and Academic Services records, 1987-2009.
Division of Student and Academic Services records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Division of Student and Academic Services records, 1987-2009.
4-16-2926
Cornell University.Division of Student and Academic Services.
25 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Manuscripts, Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, committee minutes, President's Fund files, program files, subject files, and other records relating to student and academic services and academic programs, including material from the Academic Affairs and Campus Life Committee.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Division of Campus Life and the Division of Academic Programs merged in late 1990 to become the Division of Academic Programs and Campus Life and was headed by Larry Palmer whose title went from Vice President of Academic Programs to Vice President of Academic Programs and Campus Affairs. It was not a complete merger because some departments of Academic Programs were assigned to the colleges and some departments under the Division of Campus Life (such as Police, Health Services and Athletics and Physical Education) were not incorporated in the merger, but rather were assigned to the then Senior Vice President. In 1994, Susan Murphy became Vice President of Student and Academic Services, replacing the Vice President of Academic Programs and Campus Affairs. Some departments within the Division, such as the Museum, Cornell Press, Cornell in Washington,and ROTC, were reassigned to the then Vice President, John Weisenfeld. In 1995, Susan Murphy took responsibility for Athletics and University Health Services, but the Division did not change names.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, committee minutes, President's Fund files, program files, subject files, and other records relating to student and academic services and academic programs, including material from the Academic Affairs and Campus Life Committee.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Adams, Barry B., 1935-; Murphy, Susan Hills.; Palmer, Larry I., 1944-; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University.Office of the Vice President for Academic Programs.; Cornell University.Office of the Vice Provost.; Cornell University.Office of the Vice President for Academic Programs and Campus Life.; Cornell University.Academic Affairs and Campus Life Committee.; Cornell University.Division of Student and Academic Services.; Cornell University.Division of Campus Life.; Cornell University.Division of Academic Programs.; Cornell University.Division of Campus Life and Academic Programs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to the permission of the office of origin.
RELATED MATERIALS
See also Vice President for Campus Affairs, Division of Campus Life Records, #4-6-1621
CONTAINER LIST
- Associate Deans Group, prev - May 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Associate Deans Group, June 1987 - Jan 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Associate Deans Group, February 1988 - November 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Associate Deans Group, December 1988 - December 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Associate Deans Group, January 1990 - May 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Associate Deans Group, June 1990 - May 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Amoco Award for Excellence in Teaching, April 19 1990 - July 8 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Cornell in Washington (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Olin Corporation Charitable Trust Summer Project Grant (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Forensics, July 1 1982 - December 2 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Freshman Writing Program, Fall 1980 - November 21 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Hunter College Program - Students, May 22 1990 - January 20 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Hunter College Program - Correspondence, December 21 1988 - December 20 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Hunter College Program - Correspondence, January 4 1991 - November 12 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Lab of Ornithology, March 17 1989 - August 12 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Lab of Ornithology, September 7 1987 - December 9 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Reorganization and Merge of Campus Life and Academic Programs, 1990 - 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Mellon Foundation "Fresh Combinations" Grant, June 1986 - April 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Mellon Foundation "Fresh Combinations" Grant, May 1983 - February 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Multicultural Education, 1989 - 1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Hispanic American Studies, 1990 - 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Dean of Students Review, 1987 - 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Ethnic Studies Funding, 1986 - 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Student Assembly Finance Commission, Fall 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Big Red Barn, 1990 - 1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Telluride Association, 1989 - 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Veterinary Medicine Academic Calender, 1991 - 1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Dean of Students Structure Issue, 1987 - 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Student Management Corporation, 1992 - 1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Arts and Sciences Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1989 - 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Bursar Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1983 - 1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Engineering Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1988 - 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Ethics and Public Life, 1985 - 1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Graduate Student Life - The Henry, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Cornell Cinema, January 31 1984 - July 13 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Peace Studies, December 21 1982 - March 26 1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- German Academic Exchange Service (DAAD) Summer Program (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Career Center: Recruitment on Campus, March 15 1985 - March 16 1987 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Undergraduate Education - Remarks by Larry I. Palmer, July 27 1987 - September 9 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Undergraduate Education, March 22 1978 - December 22 1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Protests, Spring 1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Architecture, Art and Planning, 1988 - 1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Advising - Ziegler Report, 1982 - 1992 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Gulf War - Flag Issue, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- American Indian Program House- File 1 of 5, 1987 - 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- American Indian Program House- File 2 of 5, 1987 - 1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- American Indian Program House- File 3 of 5, 1987 - 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- American Indian Program House- File 4 of 5, 1987 - 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- American Indian Program House- File 5 of 5, 1987 - 1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Clare Booth Luce Foundation, 1987 - 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Henry Luce Foundation, 1983 - 1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Keasbey Foundation, 1987 - 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Sears Foundation, 1988 - 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Dana Foundation, 1986 - 1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Atlantic Service Foundation, 1983 - 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- SURDNA Foundation, 1982 - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Ford Foundation, 1987 - 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Ford Foundation, 1988 - 1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Ford Foundation - Correspondence, 1990 - 1994 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Ford Foundation, 1991 - 1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Pew Foundation - Proposal Undergraduate Science Education, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Pew Foundation - Report Undergraduate Science Education, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Pew Foundation - Science Symposium, 1987 - 1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Pew Foundation - General Correspondence, 1986 - 1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Pew Foundation - Math and Science Education, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Pew Foundation - Math and Science Education, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Pew Foundation - Math and Science Education, 1990 - 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- PSC - Insurance for Student Volunteers in Community, 1990 - 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Hotel/ILR Agreement, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- International TA Training Program, 1989 - 1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Kramnick Report, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Residential Committee, 1990 - 1992 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Faculty in Residence, 1990 - 1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Faculty in Residence, 1983 - 1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Faculty in Residence - Annual Reports, Handbooks, Brochures, 1986 - 1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Miss Evers Boys - Video (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Miss Evers Boys - Council Weekend Panel Discussion (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Miss Evers Boys - Fundraising, June 10 1991 - December 21 1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Miss Evers Boys - Fundraising, May 1 1991 - June 9 1991 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Miss Evers Boys - Fundraising, February 1990 - April 1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Miss Evers Boys - General Correspondence, August 1991 - June 1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Miss Evers Boys - General Correspondence, June 1991 - July 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Miss Evers Boys - General Correspondence, January 1990 - May 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Miss Evers Boys - Minnesota Symposium (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Miss Evers Boys - Nursing Alumni Reading (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Miss Evers Boys - The Play (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Miss Evers Boys - Theater Production (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Miss Evers Boys - Tuskegee Study Article (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Miss Evers Boys - Study Guide and Video Planning Budget, March 1992 - May 1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Miss Evers Boys - Study Guide and Video Planning Budget, 1991 - February 1992 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Academic Affairs Committee - Pre-Academic Affairs Committee, 1960 - 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Academic Affairs Committee - Pre-Academic Affairs Committee, 1977 - 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Academic Affairs Committee - Pre-Academic Affairs Committee, 1978 - 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Academic Affairs Committee, 1979 - 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Academic Affairs Committee, 1981 - 1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Academic Affairs Committee, 1982 - 1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Academic Affairs Committee - Subcommittee on Minority Education #1, 1982 - 1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Academic Affairs Committee - Subcommittee on Minority Education #2, 1982 - 1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Academic Affairs Committee, 1983 - 1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Academic Affairs Committee #1, 1934 - 1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Academic Affairs Committee #2, 1984 - 1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Academic Affairs Committee, 1985 - 1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Academic Affairs Committee #1, 1986 - 1987 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Academic Affairs Committee #2, 1986 - 1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Academic Affairs Committee #3, 1986 - 1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Academic Affairs Committee #4, 1986 - 1987 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Academic Affairs Committee #1, 1987 - 1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Academic Affairs Committee #2, 1987 - 1988 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Academic Affairs Committee #3, 1987 - 1988 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Academic Affairs Committee #4, 1987 - 1988 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Academic Affairs Committee #1, 1988 - 1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Academic Affairs Committee #2, 1988 - 1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Academic Affairs Committee #3, 1988 - 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Academic Affairs Committee #4, 1988 - 1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Academic Affairs Committee #5, 1988 - 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Academic Affairs Committee #1, 1989 - 1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Academic Affairs Committee #2, 1989 - 1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Academic Affairs Committee #3, 1989 - 1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Academic Affairs Committee #4, 1989 - 1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Academic Affairs Committee #5, 1989 - 1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Academic Affairs Committee #1, 1990 - 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Academic Affairs Committee #2, 1990 - 1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- President's Fund
  - PFEI General Information All Years (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - PFEI General Correspondence, 1987 - 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - PFEI General Correspondence, 1990 - 1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1992 - 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Round I General Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Funding Decisions (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Asian-American Studies Program (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Common Learning Course on Controversial Social Issues (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Course in "Economics for the Citizen" (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Course on Islamic-Judaic Relations (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Course in Natural Resources and Environmental Policies (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Hispanic-American Studies Program (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Housing and Feeding the Less Fortunate (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Improvement of Teacher Training and Special Materials for Bio Sciences (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - International Teaching Assistants (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Korean Literature (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - "Learning How to Learn" - Intro Nutrition Course (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Office of Instructional Support (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Career Advising in Arts and Sciences (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Cross-College Advising (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Computer Network (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Improvement of Facilities in Bailey and Uris Halls (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Residence Life Academic Learning Program/Environment (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Redesign Intro Chem for Non-Majors (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Toni Morrison Distinguished Visitors (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Undergraduate Course about Africa (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Use of Library Resources (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Course on Social Responsibilities and Institutions (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Educational Program for Pre-Vets (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Engineering Tutorial (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Engineering Writing Program (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - General Education Course in Evolution (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Gender in the Classroom (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - PFEI not funded #1 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - PFEI not funded #2 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - PFEI not funded #3 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Announcements (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Agenda/Minutes (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Project Progress Reports (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Donor Reports (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Projects Sampled (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Finances (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Data Rounds 1-8 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Projects Report Data (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Samples (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - NSF Matches (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Backup Material for Audit (Box 11, Folder 12)
- President's Fund Round II
  - Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Transfers (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Community Service Learning Projects in Field-Based Course (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Computer Assisted Writing in Iroquois Languages (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Conference on Scientific Literacy: Curriculum and Pedagogy (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - A Freshman Course: Intro to Study of Medicine (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Implications of Science (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Electronic Music (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Improve Student Persistence by Enhancing Achievement and Expanding Career Development (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Integrated Stats and Matrix Computer Programs for Improving Undergraduate Education (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Jazz Ensembles (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Integrative Proposal to Improve Quality of Undergraduate Education (I) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - An Introduction to China (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Intro Course in Design Fundamentals for Non-Majors (III) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Intro to Recombinant DNA Technology...with Hypertext on MAC and PC (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Peer Perspective (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Public Policy Process in Albany (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Toward a Consolidated Media Capability for Teaching on the Arts Quad (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Redesign of Sophomore Engineering Mathematics Courses (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Video for the Enrichment of Non-Majors Introductory Biology (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Videodiscs for Teaching the Course "Cultural Entomology" (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - A Visual Learning Laboratory (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - PFEI not funded #1 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - PFEI not funded #2 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- President's Fund Round III
  - General Information and Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Transfers (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Anthropology and Archeology (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Course in Ethnic, Third-World, Colonial, and Post-Colonial Literature (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Freshmen Chem Lab: Modernization and Diversification (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - A Hypertext Tutorial Work Station in Plant Anatomy (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Improvements for the Astronomy Introductory Courses (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Intro Course in Communist Studies (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Introduction to Near Eastern Civilization (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Major Laboratory Upgrade for Physics 112 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Microcomputer-Assisted Materials for Learning Advanced...Vocabulary (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Molecular Messengers in Nature (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Plant Communities in the Landscape (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Proposal for Broadening African Language Instruction (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Remote Tutoring for Physics 101-102 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - SIGI Plus (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Teaching Science as a process in Non-Majors Biology (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Training Program for Graduate TAs in Intro Courses in Consumer Economics and Housing (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - A Training Program for TAs (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Training Teaching Assistants in Intro English Courses (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Use of Hypercard for Innovative in AE102/CS102 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Waste Management - A Systems Approach (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Videotapes to Improve Undergraduate Advising Instructional Skills and TA Training (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Urban American and the Year 2000 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- President's Fund Round IV
  - General Information and Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Contemporary Issues (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Establishing CD-ROM Library Reference Service for Undergraduates (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Expansion of the Role of Writing in Upper-Division Arts and Sciences Courses (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Hughs Institute Proposal Development (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Maintaining the Momentum (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - South Asia Slide Project (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Support for College of Human Ecology (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Teaching Assistant Training Program in ILR (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Women's Studies (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - PFEI not funded (Box 10, Folder 6)
- President's Fund Round V
  - General Information/Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - CISER Initiative to Support Undergraduate Honors Research (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Engineering Writing Program (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - The Engineering Tutorial (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Language Education: Beginning to Plan for the Future (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Information Technology and Literary for Bio Sciecnes Undergraduates (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Teaching Policy Analysis with a Large-Scale Simulation Model (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Workshops on Teaching for Graduate Students at Cornell (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - PFEI not funded (Box 10, Folder 15)
- President's Fund Round VI
  - General Information/Correspondence #1 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence #2 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Bachelor's Degree in Engineering/International Studies (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "Cornell Conference on the Enhancement of Science and Math Education" (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Fellow-in-Service Program (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Professors Emeriti Tutorial Project (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Innovations in Language Instruction (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Improvement of Teaching Facilities (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Reading and Literacy Center in Harlem (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Task Force on Quality of Undergraduate Teaching (Box 10, Folder 25)
- President's Fund Round VII
  - Round VII (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Engineering in Context (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Freshman Hands-On Instruction Laboratory (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Multicultural Living and Learning Project (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Anthropology and Education in Cultural Diversity (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Additional Money for McMillan (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Classroom Scheduling (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - International (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Miss Evers' Boys Production (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Multicultural/Diversity Project (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Public Service Center (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Renovations of Classrooms (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Task Force on Economics Education (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Curriculum Renovation Project for Physics 101-102, Robert Cotts (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Student Committee (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - PFEI not funded (Box 10, Folder 41)
- President's Fund Round VIII
  - Round VIII (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Campus Life/Ujamaa, 1989 - 1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Alcohol Policy, 1985 - 1989 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Sport Clubs (Box 12, Folder 3)
- CURW - Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Fee vs. General Purpose (UHS) (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Rugby 1992 - 1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- FIPSE Alcohol Grant (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Parents Program (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Greek Relations Committee (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Inspections/Financing (F/S) (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Fraternity Loan Program, 1986 - 1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Alpha Delta Phi (Box 12, Folder 12)
- RA Training Incident (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Student Assembly, 1991 - 1992 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Student Assembly, 1992 - 1993 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Student Assembly, 1993 - 1994 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Student Assembly, 1994 - 1995 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Student Assembly, 1995 - 1996 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Student Assembly, 1996 - 1997 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Athletics Admissions System (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Athletics and Physical Education (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Athletics and Physical Education Review (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Athletics Audit (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Athletics Vision 2000 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Football TV Contract (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Hockey Compliance Review, 1993 - 1994 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Hockey Compliance Review, 1995 - 1996 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Hockey Housing (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Hockey Issues, 1978, 1982 - 1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- NCAA Revenue Sharing (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Physical Therapy Space (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Title IX (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Ivy Policy Committee, 1985 - 1988 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Ivy Policy Committee, 1988 - 1989 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Ivy Policy Committee, 1989 - 1990 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Ivy Policy Committee, 1990 - 1991 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Ivy Policy Committee, 1991 - 1992 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Campus Life Housing Reports Residential Committee, 1992 - 1997 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Ivy Council of Presidents, 1988 -1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Ivy Policy Committees, 1992 - 1993 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Ivy Policy Committees, 1993 - 1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Ivy Policy Committees, 1994 - 1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Ivy Policy Committees, 1995 - 1996 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Ivy Policy Committees, 1996 - 1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- State Department of Education Inquiry/Myer (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Student Assembly, 1997 - 1998 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Annual Reports and Planning Docs, 1990/1991 - 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Associate Deans Group, 1990 - 1992 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Associate Deans Group, 1992 - 1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Associate Deans Group, 1994 - 1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Associate Deans Group, 1995 - 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Campus Life and Local Law Committee, 1991 - 1993 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- GLB Working Group, 1993 - 1997 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- H.F. Johnson Museum of Art, 1981 - 1986 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Latino Living Center, 1993 - 1996 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Latino Student Concerns (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Program Review, 1996 - 1997 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Rewards Committee, 1993 - 1996 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- SAS Divisional Meetings, 1995 - 2000 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- SAS Strategic Planning, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Study Space (Box 15, Folder 15)
- U.S. Department of Education, 1996 - 1997 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1986 - 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1986 - 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life- including Report on the Reorganization of Student Services (1990), 1986 - 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1990 - 1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1990 - 1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1990 - 1991 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1991 - 1992 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1992 - 1993 (Box 16, Folder 8)